questions = {
    "easy": [
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Rosanii's Instagram account?",
            "options": ["rosanii.writes", "starlightviolet", "galactic_violet", "violetinspace"],
            "answer": "rosanii.writes"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are Aquarians?",
            "options": ["Creatures from mythology", "Characters from The Blue Saga",
                        "People born under a specific zodiac sign", "Alien species from Rosanii's sci-fi universe"],
            "answer": "Characters from The Blue Saga"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the main character of 'The Blue Saga'?",
            "options": ["Gabriela", "Ariel", "N", "Nathaniel"],
            "answer": "Gabriela"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the main character of 'The Rule of change'",
            "options": ["Nathaniel", "Gabriela",  "N", "Merkav"],
            "answer": "Nathaniel"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Bechdel test?",
            "options": ["A test for gender bias in works of fiction", "A psychological assessment tool",
                        "A physical fitness exam", "A test for color blindness"],
            "answer": "A test for gender bias in works of fiction"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is name of autor of 'The Rule of change' and 'The Blue Saga'?",
            "options": ["Violet", "Viola", "Violetka", "Violetta"],
            "answer": "Violet"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Mary Sue?",
            "options": ["character who is be too perfect and unrealistic", "author of 'The Rule of change' and 'The Blue Saga'",
                        "Main characte of 'The Rule of change'", "Main characte of 'The Blue Saga'"],
            "answer": "character who is be too perfect and unrealistic"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are Singulars?",
            "options": [
                "People with unnatural abilities",
                "People who are genetically modified",
                "People who have undergone extreme training",
                "people who can live under water"
            ],
            "answer": "People with unnatural abilities"
        }
    ],
    "medium": [
        {
            "question": "What is Tolkienism?",
            "options": ["Copying the style of J.R.R. Tolkien", "The worship of Tolkien as a deity",
                        "The community of fans of J.R.R. Tolkien's works and adaptations", "A subgenre of science fiction"],
            "answer": "Copying the style of J.R.R. Tolkien"
        },
        {
            "question": "Singulars Lower Order are ...",
            "options": ["Unyielding", "Persistent", "Navigators", "Anomalies"],
            "answer": "Unyielding"
        },
        {
            "question": "Singulars of the Highest Order are ...",
            "options": ["Unyielding", "Persistent", "Navigators", "Anomalies"],
            "answer": "Anomalies"
        },
        {
            "question": "What nationality is Nathaniel?",
            "options": ["Polish", "Swedish", "Finnish", "Israeli"],
            "answer": "Polish"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who are the Navigators?",
            "options": [
                "A Singulars of the Higher Order",
                "A group of advanced humans who use the spice melange to fold space and navigate interstellar travel",
                "A group of seafarers who explore the oceans in the world of he Blue Saga",
                "A secret society of writers who writes like Tolkien"
            ],
            "answer": "A Singulars of the Higher Order"
        }
    ],
    "hard": [
        {
            "question": "What abilities do Anomalies in 'The Rule of Change' universe?",
            "options": ["They have a superconsciousness", "They have a subconscious",
                        "They are physically fit", "They can live under water"],
            "answer": "They have a superconsciousness"
        },
        {
            "question": "What means The Rule of change?",
            "options": ["A new kind of Singulars appears", "The old house transfers power to another",
                        "The Singulars distances itself from people.", "The number of Singulars is constant"],
            "answer": "A new kind of Singulars appears"
        },
        {
            "question": "What means a The Rule of donut?",
            "options": ["Oliver didn't deserve a donut", "The world is a donut", "The world is on a donut", "It's a trap"],
            "answer": "Oliver didn't deserve a donut"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who are the members of N's Four?",
          "options": [
            "N, Tulia Sara, Dalisto, John",
            "Nataniel, Tulia Sara, Dalisto, John",
            "Violet, Rosanii, Lili, Margaret",
            "Tomás, Carax, Penélope, Fumero"
          ],
          "answer": "N, Tulia Sara, Dalisto, John"
        },
    ]
}

